Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
[EDM plays]
Right there.
That’s 350.
And?
That’s everything I have. man.
That’s my rent money.
Well. you’re
short. 475. I know.
I can get you the rest
by Friday. I can...
Then come back Friday.
[EDM continues playing]
[phone ringing]
Okay. okay. but...
$825 for an alternator?
- Yeah.
- Come on. for real? Wh...
It’s a $400 part
and I could swap it out
myself in half an hour
if I had the right tools.
so it’s not really...
I’m not having
this conversation.
The thing is. I drive
deliveries. you know?
Uh-huh? So. um. I need
the van to make money.
Without the van. there’s no
way for me to pay you back.
Give me the goddamn
money you owe me.
or get the fuck out of my face.
Now. where are the
goddamn keys to the Kia?
[phone ringing]
Main ramp. [phone ringing]
Hey. baby girl. [Amy] Oh.
so you answer when I call.
What? You don’t care.
I know you don’t.
because she’s calling me.
telling me you fucking
ghosted your own daughter.
[father] I know. everything’s
running behind. [bell rings]
I’ll grab her when
I’m done here. okay?
[Amy] I can’t believe you’re
doing this shit again.
You know Wednesday and
Friday are your days.
You never prioritize her.
You know I don’t like her
riding her scooter home alone.
She’s literally sitting
out there waiting for you.
Tell her I’m sorry.
When you ask me what
it is you can do
to fix things between us.
this would be an example
of the kind of
shit I’m done with.
[line beeps]
[car horn blaring]
[EDM plays]
[bolt clicking]
Cool bike. Mm.
I always wanted to
teach my daughter.
You wanna buy it? 75 bucks.
I don’t have any money. Then
get the fuck out of here.
Calm down.
Relax. man.
[techno music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[suspenseful music plays]
Karl. Come on. Karl.
it’s just sitting there.
Not doing either of us any good.
Let me work off the
difference. yeah?
You know me. I’m good with cars.
I can... I can...
I can fix anything.
Listen to me. you
little fuck. 475.
Until then. we are done talking.
Come on. man...
What did I tell you.
huh? Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Take it easy. man. you’re pinching
me. Ah! You’re pinching me.
You want me to hurt him?
No. he doesn’t. he doesn’t.
Butter. Butter. Butter...
Ah. you got my nipple.
[tools clang]
[rhythmic drum plays]
[man] Like. they charged
me 15 bucks for a latte
and then the homeless guys
are still handling me.
[woman] We’re across the street
from that fusion restaurant
we went to the other day.
[exhaling]
It’s Eddie.
Yeah. listen. I
hate to ask. but...
[line beeps]
Hello?
Listen. call me back. okay?
Um. I’m getting
my shit together.
I’m working now.
How’s it going? How’s your mom?
Oh. okay.
[tense music plays]
Hey. man. how’s it
going? It’s Eddie.
[line beeps]
Hello?
[Eddie] Fuck!
[cash register beeping]
Can I get three
scratchers as well?
Mm-hmm.
[store bell rings]
Ah. fuck!
[tense music plays]
[rhythmic drum plays]
Yeah. listen. so I hate
to ask. but could you...
could you spot me some cash?
’Cause... Hello? [line beeps]
Fuck this. fuck.
Hey. for your
troubles. God bless.
Do I look like a
fucking junkie to you?
[grunts]
[dog barks] Oh. shit!
[dog barks] [laughs]
Are you all right
in there. buddy?
[dog whines]
Hey. Hey. buddy.
Hey. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. I’m having
a rough day too.
Want some water?
It must be hot in there.
[dog whines]
Here you go.
That’s a good boy.
There you go.
[phone ringing]
Hey. lovebug.
Don’t call me lovebug. You
promised you were coming today!
Um. hey. [Sarah] Don’t hey me.
Hey. yeah. Um...
Did your mom come grab you?
Yeah. but I didn’t
bring my scooter.
so I was stuck with Miss
Kaplan for two hours.
I’m sorry.
You know. I just got caught
up with a few things.
and you know. your mom.
she’s just better at
this kind of stuff
than I am. and...
I gotta go. I gotta go to work.
Dad? Yeah?
I still love you.
even when you’re acting
like a fart-head.
[chuckles]
Well. I still love you.
even when you smell
like turd jelly.
[scoffs] I don’t
smell like turd jelly!
Yeah. you do. and
I still love you.
All right. I gotta go for real.
[Sarah] See you.
[tense music playing]
[distant helicopter whirring]
[sighs] Okay.
Wow. this is nice.
Dolus.
Okay. okay. okay.
Let’s see what we got here.
Come on. there’s gotta
be something I can sell.
[tense music continues]
Sunglasses.
Ooh.
[whistles]
Oh. shit.
[unzipping]
All right. fuck this.
[jiggling handle]
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
[jiggles handle]
Fuck!
[tense music playing]
[panting]
Ah. Okay. Okay.
okay. okay. okay.
[grunts]
[winces]
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on.
[grunting]
[shouting] Fuck!
[intense music playing]
[rattles] Oh. shit.
Okay.
[button clicking]
What the fuck’s going on?
[phone ringing]
Fuck this!
[ringing continues]
Not answering that.
The fuck with this car?
[panting]
All right.
Good.
Fuck. [phone ringing]
Fuck you.
[ringing continues]
[screams]
Goddamn it. fucking.
fucking. fuck!
[panting]
[phone ringing]
Fuck you!
[grunts] [phone ringing]
Fuck off!
Okay. here we go.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
[ringing continues]
[winces]
[screams] Fuck! Oh. shit.
[phone ringing]
[metal clangs]
[panting]
[phone ringing]
Okay.
[phone keypad beeping]
[line beeps]
Fuck!
[ringing continues]
[laughing]
[sobbing]
[ringing continues]
All right.
[suspenseful music plays]
[caller] Hello?
Hello?
Hello. can you hear me?
Are you there?
Yeah.
[caller] Oh. jolly good.
Welcome aboard.
My name is William.
[William] Are you
there? What do you want?
[William] Well. I’m
the owner of this car.
Fuck! [William] Is that all
you have to say for yourself.
is "fuck"?
Yeah. it’s short for
"go fuck yourself!"
[William] Interesting point.
[zapping]
Did you just fucking tase
me? What is this shit?
[William laughs] Well. do
I have your attention now?
Let me out!
[William] No. I need
to explain a few things
so that we understand
each other.
Are you ready to listen?
I know you’re a little
confused. so I’ll speak slowly.
My car has been broken into six
times without a single arrest.
You understand? Okay.
[William] It does sound like
an exaggeration. doesn’t it?
Plus you today.
that makes it seven.
Listen. I don’t...
I really don’t give a
shit. What do you want?
[William] Well. I want to
talk to you. that’s all.
Fuck that! Let me out.
[William] No. no. no. not
until we get acquainted.
’til we understand each other.
Nah. let me out!
Out. out. out. out. out.
out of the fucking car!
[William] Don’t be rude. You’re
so impatient. such a naughty boy.
What? Fuck this shit.
I don’t have time
for this. seriously.
Fuck this car.
[screams] Fuck!
I just shot myself!
[William] Hello? What’s
happening down there?
Help! [William] What was that?
Help!
Sorry. it’s really
hard to understand you
when you’re screaming.
Let me turn this down a
bit. Fuck! No. no. no. no.
Now let me see
which button is...
[zapping] [William]
Oh. sorry about that.
Sorry. sorry. sorry.
sorry. Motherfu...
[William] My mistake. No.
it’s not that one. no.
Do I press here? I
think. let me see.
No. no. it’s not that one.
That’s a lot of blood!
I think I press here?
Help! [William]
Hang on a second.
Be patient with me. yes?
[keys jingling]
I just shot myself. Just
fucking... Press here. Let me see.
Let me consult the
manual a moment.
Hey! Hey!
Help me! Help! [William] Two.
No. I think. hang on a second.
Help! Help! Help!
[siren blaring]
[gasps]
Hey! Help me!
What the fuck?
Help me!
God. goddamn it!
[William] Ah. here we are.
Yes. I think this is it. Good.
[groaning]
Fuck.[William]
Are you all right?
Oh. shit! [William]
That didn’t sound good.
That’s a lot of blood.
I do hope you’re not bleeding
all over the inside of my car.
[panting] Fuck.
Call the cops. I don’t care.
Now! I’m not playing. Call 911.
[William] I’m sorry to report that
would be a complete waste of time.
You see. the police
are far too busy.
I need an ambulance.
man. I need help.
[William] Oh. you’re
in luck. I’m a doctor.
What seems to be the
trouble. my friend?
Fuck.
Motherfucker. Fuck.
God. God! [line beeping]
Just open the fucking
door and let me out. okay?
[William] How bad is
it? It’s bad. It’s bad.
I can’t stop the bleeding.
[William] Well. that wasn’t very
clever of you. was it. old sport?
The walls and glass
are bulletproof.
I’m not feeling right.
I think I’m dying.
[William] Oh. I doubt it.
If you’d hit an artery.
you would already be
unconscious or possibly dead.
No. no. no. no.
[William] Anyway.
let me tell you
about the SUV you broke into.
Goddamn it. I don’t
care about that.
[William] But I really
think you should care
’cause I cannot think about
anything more relevant
to your current situation.
Are you listening to me.
man? I need medical help now.
[William] The vehicle you
broke into belongs to me
and quite simply.
I have had enough.
My leg is burning.
[William] First.
I have to ask you.
did you really think
a vehicle like this
would be left unlocked?
I’m hurt. man. I’m dying.
[William] I don’t care. I set
a trap. and you took the bait.
Simple as that.
You couldn’t resist.
and now you’re mine to
do with as I please.
I can’t feel my leg.
[William] But I thought you were
burning. Now you cannot feel it.
Well. it’s both.
[William] It cannot be both.
[screams] It’s both!
[William] The interior
is soundproofed.
I’ve also jammed the cellular.
Bluetooth. and the Wi-Fi...
You’re a fucking psycho!
[William] Psychopath? Me?
No one has ever called
me a psychopath before.
At least I don’t think so.
Though I am quite sure
all this is rational.
This project has been
planned meticulously.
every detail carefully reviewed.
Every eventuality anticipated.
What do you want? I want
you to pay attention.
Please. man. I need
you to listen carefully
to every word I speak.
Fuck you!
[zapping]
You mother... You motherfucker!
[William] Sorry. I didn’t
hear that. What did you say?
I didn’t say anything. I
didn’t say anything. man.
[William] Good. now are
you ready to listen?
No. No. clearly not.
[William] What is important
to me is that you understand
the pain that you cause.
I want you to be truly sorry
and experience the
consequences of your actions.
Do you understand? Okay.
Okay. man. I’m sorry.
[William] Good. good. I’m
sorry. You win. I’m sorry.
[William] Okay. then I’ll
start the ball rolling.
You already know my
name. My name is William.
I’m a widower. That
means my wife is dead.
or my wife died recently.
something like that.
But now. I was born in a small
industrial town in South Wales.
You’ve probably never
heard of South Wales.
That’s no matter.
I’m going. man.
[William speaking in Welsh]
Bit of Welsh for you.
Anyway. I moved here
to the United States
when I was seven.
And I have lived
here most of my life.
in this city. in the
same neighborhood.
And this is an
upscale neighborhood.
You wouldn’t know
it by looking at it.
but there isn’t a lot for under a
million dollars. Can you believe it?
I need water.
[William] Shut up.
- You’ll be fine.
- No. no.
Anyway. without
water you can make it
for at least another 48
hours. Doctor taught me.
And what was I saying?
Oh. the neighborhood. It hasn’t
changed since I was a boy.
Oh. God.
[William] We left our
front doors unlocked.
People had pride in how they
looked and how they behaved.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[sinister music plays]
[grunting]
[panting]
Oh. no.
[sinister music plays]
[phone ringing]
[William] You know something? I
don’t actually need you to accept.
So let’s try again. shall we?
I’m fucking starving.
[William] Please watch your
language. I hate vulgarity.
What do you want from me?
[William] Well. it is important
that we understand each other.
Just give me food and water. and
I’ll listen to you drone on forever.
[William] Okay. well. I bought
my daughter a condominium
just a few blocks from here.
There was a small yard. high
ceilings. nice light. nothing fancy.
It was the perfect
home to start a family.
And then. when was it?
It was two years ago.
in December. I think.
Anyway. I took her shopping.
We went to the outlet mall.
We had lunch at Emma’s
favorite restaurant.
It was a perfect day.
And when I dropped her off at the
condominium. two men approached...
Listen. I don’t give a
shit about your life story.
I need food and water
now. motherfucker.
[William] Language! [zapping]
Jesus! Fuck!
[zapping] [screams]
You motherfucking
fucking. seriously.
language motherfucking what?
[William] Here we go. yeah.
[laughing] [AC blowing]
Oh. no. don’t... don’t
air condition me.
[yodeling on radio]
You sick...
[yodeling continues
louder] Ugh.
Ugh!
Not a bad song.
It’s not a bad song.
[yodeling continues]
Fucking shut up!
[Eddie screams]
Sorry. all right?
Turn off the song.
[yodeling continues]
[screaming]
[yodeling stops]
[rain pattering]
[horn blaring]
[yodeling resumes]
[shuddering]
[yodeling stops]
[phone ringing]
I’m sorry for cursing.
I won’t do it again.
[AC stops]
[sighs]
[car honking]
[siren blaring]
[helicopter whirring]
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[dripping]
[metal clanging]
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
[William] Good
morning. old sport.
Hah. Oh. you look
terrible down there.
I think a more accurate
word would be "ghastly."
Yeah. that’s it. Ghastly.
That’s probably the first stage
of starvation. isn’t it? Hmm.
Are you having
trouble concentrating?
How often do you
think about food?
Are you irritable?
I think I’ll just put a "yes"
down for that one. okay?
Have you thought this
through. huh? Like at all?
If I die. what are you
gonna do with my body?
And disposing of a body.
that can’t be easy.
Not in a city with
cameras everywhere.
And how will you live with it?
[William] I don’t
care. really.
Nobody will miss
you. [munching]
Have you read Crime and
Punishment? Dostoevsky?
[William] Yeah. long
time ago. have you?
Yeah.
What. you think I’m illiterate.
just because I don’t
have any money.
I can’t read? I read.
[William] College?
I’m self-taught.
I know that’s hard for you fancy.
spoon-fed types to understand.
but street smarts are important.
[William] Street
smarts. ah. yes.
Perhaps I should have
studied that instead. yeah.
[zapping]
[William laughs]
I suggest you leave
the cameras alone.
That was not very street
smart. was it? No.
My point. and the point
of Crime and Punishment
is that killing someone will
fuck... [William] Language.
Eff you up.
I’ve done a lot of
effed up sh... stuff.
but I’ve never killed anyone.
I could never and I
would never kill anyone.
It’s a different level.
[William] Thus spake the
man carrying the gun.
Well. that’s different.
That’s for protection.
Where I’m from. the cops
don’t show up when you call.
[William] Yes. I
have noticed that.
but if the police were
free to do their job.
do you think I would
have built this vehicle?
So we agree on something. huh?
We have something in common.
[William] Yes. well.
we all breathe oxygen
and we all die in
the end. don’t we?
Help me out here.
man. I’m dying.
[William] We also
have that in common
because I’m dying too.
of prostate cancer.
Optimistically. I have about four months
to live. I think. Something like that.
I’m so sorry to hear that.
[William] But that is why
I’m doing this. you see?
I want to make a
difference. I want justice.
Then call the cops.
Have me arrested. I’ll confess.
That’s justice. right?
[William] Well. the problem
is rather complicated.
The whole judicial system. the
police. the prosecutors. the judges.
no longer have any power
because they have all
been castrated by sheep.
the bleeding-heart
governors of our states.
the spineless. creepy
little busybody bastards
who care nothing about
the people of this country
but choose instead to give
pestilent little shits like you
a little slap on the wrist.
coddling you. babying you.
giving you free rent and food.
not forgetting. of course.
the mandatory touchy-feely
psychotherapist fuckwits
who help you to process
the grief... What the fuck?
...of your victimhood.
So for justice. I must
blaze my own path.
You think this is just?
Really. what you’re
doing to me here?
[William] Well. let
me put it this way.
In some countries. if
you were caught stealing.
they would cut your hand off.
No. That’s not true.
Everybody says that they cut your
hands off. but it’s not true.
Really? Yeah.
For most offenses. they
just send you to jail
like anywhere else.
What about serious
offenders. repeat offenders?
What about ’em?
[William] What is
their punishment?
Four fingers.
[William] Really? Then give me
your social security number.
and I will check.
Check what?
[William] If this is
your first offense.
I’ll let you go. but if
you’re a repeat offender.
as I suspect. then you will
confess and apologize to me.
and then I will cut off
four of your fingers.
You... You’re serious?
[William] Oh. yes.
Yes. deadly serious.
Do you accept?
No. why would I
possibly accept that?
[William] Well.
think carefully.
This is a one-time offer.
but I give you my word.
That’s not justice.
Well. it seems fair
to me. old sport.
Not when the system is rigged.
[William] So what? It’s
always been rigged!
Did the system make you
break into my vehicle?
Or is it just that most people in this
country live paycheck to paycheck?
Here we go again with your socialistic...
That they can’t buy medicine.
Communist Manifesto!
They can’t pay rent.
They can’t afford
anything. Huh?
[William] Distribute
that with your needles.
Nonsense! Everyone has
the same opportunity.
No. no. no. The real crime is that
this city is full of poor people.
but the laws are made by
rich people for rich people.
It’s sick!
[William] That’s
right. comrade.
And you are entitled
to what? To everything?
The laws are written
so people like you
can keep what you have and
keep everyone else down.
You’re the criminal.
[William] Oh. I am sorry.
Have you been triggered?
Did I hurt your feelings?
No. I’m not triggered.
How much did you spend on
this thing anyway. huh?
A hundred thousand?
[William] I have no idea.
I have so much money.
it is hard to keep
track of it all.
You deserve to be robbed.
[William] Yes. but I
earned every penny.
Yeah. right. with no help
from your family. huh?
Who paid for medical school?
You think this is about
privilege. but it is not.
It’s about right and wrong.
I started with nothing.
but instead of feeling
sorry for myself.
I worked and worked.
and I made a good
life for myself.
Yeah. you seem
like you have made
a wonderful fucking life
for yourself. you sick fuck!
[zapping] [screams]
My point...
My point is that you can’t
have justice without morality.
and you have none.
[William] I read somewhere.
thou shalt not steal.
I think it was in the Bible.
"Thou shalt not steal."
That’s not complicated. is it?
But if you do have
a problem with that.
you can always take it up
with God. or Karl Marx.
or the Kardashians. or anyone.
But it’s something I do not need
to debate with you. Bye-bye!
[yodeling on radio]
[music stops]
[sirens wailing]
[music resumes]
[yodeling on radio]
[yodeling continues]
[gags]
[gags. coughs]
Fuck.
[music stops] [William] Aw.
I really thought you were
going to go through with it.
Why bother stitching me
up just to let me die?
[William] Let you die?
You’ve got to be kidding me.
No. no. I’ve invested a lot of
time and money into this project.
and I want to enjoy it.
I need to have some fun
in these final days.
Do you understand?
So tell me your social
security number.
I already said no.
[William] Give me your
first and your last name.
If you give me your
social security number.
I will give you some water.
and I will turn off the heat.
Eddie.
[William] Eddie. good. go on.
Give me the water. and
I’ll tell you the rest.
[William] Um. no. I’m sorry.
Eddie. That’s not how this works.
But I’m in no hurry. you know.
I’m just fine and
dandy sitting here
enjoying my whiskey
on the rocks.
Yes. it’s pure.
[slurps]
Oh. God! I think I
have sensitive teeth.
It happens as you age.
Did you know that?
Something to look forward to.
Eddie Barrish.
Eddie Barrish. thank you. And
social security number. please?
173.173.
2-5.2-5.
6787.
6787. Thank you
very much. Good.
Yeah. and that water?
[William] What is
the magic word?
Please.
[William] Sorry.
I didn’t hear you.
It cut out for some reason.
Please.
[William] Please. Good.
that’s better. Very good.
I hid the water bottle
under the passenger seat
when I was treating your wound.
[gasps]
[tense drum beat plays]
[scratches]
[laughing]
[phone ringing]
[William] What is so funny?
What are you laughing at?
I won.
I won $500.
That’s everything I needed.
It’s enough.
Enough to get my van back.
Enough.
I had it this whole time.
[William coughs]
Sorry. Eddie. but with cancer. one
has good nights and bad nights.
I wanna go home.
[William sighs] We can
never go home again. Eddie.
That’s life’s tragedy.
How do you pick up the
threads of an old life?
How do you go on?
When in your heart you
begin to understand
that there is no going back.
There are some things
that time cannot mend.
Some hurts that go too
deep that have taken hold.
[Eddie] It’s Lord
of the Rings. right?
[William] Yeah. That was
one of Emma’s favorites.
I need food.
And a joint.
God. I’d do anything
for a joint right now.
Look. I’m sorry. okay?
I’m sorry I broke into your car.
I shouldn’t have.
And I mean it. It’s not okay.
And you’re right. everyone
deserves to feel safe.
And I broke that bond.
And I acted selfishly.
And I tried to steal
from you. and I admit it.
And I’m sorry.
I... I...
I. honestly. I get it.
Okay. whatever my reasons.
it doesn’t make it right.
I know right from wrong.
and I made a choice
that I truly.
truly. truly regret.
You have no idea.
I’m begging you. just
not for forgiveness.
just to be the
bigger person here.
[William] Well. you might have
been right about me. Eddie.
I might be a psycho because I
don’t feel bad for you at all.
[laughs]
However. I applaud your effort.
and for that. you get a reward.
There’s a cookie
in the glove box.
[suspenseful music plays]
Well. that should keep you
going for a while. yeah?
Well. hold on a second. I
have a call on my work phone.
[phone rings]
[William] Hello? Hello?
Yeah? Well. tell me quickly.
I’m on another call.
Yeah. Okay.
Her water broke?
Any pain?
Tell reception that she
is my patient. okay?
Good. Bye. Thank you.
[feedback noise] I’m
sorry. Eddie. I have to go.
We’ll talk soon. okay?
Wait. I need water.
[William] Enjoy the cookie.
And a joint.
He’s leaving.
[panting] He’s gone. He’s gone.
[tense music plays]
[camera clicks]
Okay.
That will disable
the main power line.
Safety switch.
I’ve got to pop the
safety to unplug.
All right. Come on.
Come on.
Please. God. work.
[Eddie grunts]
Come on.
[winces]
[groaning]
Come on. Eddie. Come on.
[zapping]
God! Fuck. you’re
tasing my heart. man!
[William] Hey. what are
you doing down there?
What are you after?
I give up.
[William] From now on. keep
your hands where I can see them.
I am always watching. Eddie.
[ominous music plays]
[bird chirping]
[tense music playing]
Six-piece Chicken McNuggets.
No. no. 20-piece
Chicken McNugget meal.
A large fries.
Milk shake.
Strawberry milk shake.
[ominous music plays]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
A large Coke.
Mmm...
And a large Coke.
[gulping]
[retches]
[rain pattering]
[melancholic music plays]
[button clicks]
[exhales deeply]
[rain pattering]
[breathing deeply]
[sniffles]
[button clicking]
[engine revving]
Uh...
Okay.
Okay. uh...
All right. Okay. Let’s see
here. Let’s see. let’s see.
[engine revving]
[chuckles]
Whoa! Let’s go. yeah!
[engine revving]
[car screeches]
[groans] Oh. no.
no. no. no. come on!
Come on!
[phone ringing]
[William laughing]
Oh. Edward. Edward. Edward.
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
Oh. fuck.
[William] Surely not. You’re
smarter than that. aren’t you?
[grunts]
Fuck! Fuck!
Where you taking me. man?
[William] Tell me. Edward.
what kind of music are
you in the mood for?
Music?
[William] My daughter used to
play that one song over and over.
Drove me crazy. but
haven’t heard it for years.
Just tell me what you want.
[classical music plays]
[William] Just look at
what they’ve become. Eddie.
I mean. really look.
They’re like
animals. aren’t they?
Living off handouts.
Addicts. criminals.
And we all just go on
like this is normal.
like this is okay.
Society’s broken.
[scoffs] We are backwards.
I mean. take this neighborhood.
Looks like a safe place
to raise a family.
does it not?
So what do you see. Eddie?
I give up. Just tell me.
[William] Security systems.
cameras. metal screen doors.
These are good people who
live in fear. You get it?
[engine revving]
Whoa.
Oh. shit.
[tires screech]
[screams]
Hey. slow down.
[William] Relax. Eddie.
I’m just opening her up.
That’s all. Slow down!
[William] Have
some fun. you know.
[Eddie] Hey. where
are we going?
[William] Where are we
going? Somewhere that’s fun.
[giggles] Lots of fun.
[intense musical buildup]
[car horn honks]
[William] Here we are.
Home sweet home.
[grunts]
[metal clanking]
[sounds of fighting]
[William] Look. They
have no shame. have they?
No fear of repercussions.
What are you doing here?
[William] Well. you wanted to go
home. didn’t you? So here we are.
[car honking]
[Eddie] What are you doing?
[William] You see. these two idiots
know that the police don’t care.
They feel safe.
[engine starts]
[bones crunching] [screams]
You hit him!
[William]
Whoops-a-daisy![cackles]
Yes. why is he the only one who
gets to break the social contract?
[Eddie] No. no. no!
[car accelerating]
Stop!
Just... Just... Just
let him go. man!
[engine stops]
[Eddie] Come on.
man. just let him go.
[panting]
[Eddie] Just leave him
alone. He’s a human being!
[William] Well. I
guess it is okay
for you to break
the social contract.
and for them.
but not for me.
How is that fair?
Stop. stop. stop! Don’t!
[car crashes] [screaming]
[William] There has to be a punishment
for breaking the social contract. right?
[Eddie] Not like this.
[William] So you want anarchy.
Good. then let’s
have some anarchy.
[engine revving]
Stop. stop!
[William] But I
don’t want to stop.
If there are no rules.
then why should I?
[engine revving]
[metal squealing]
[wailing. screaming]
[William] He’s a gangster.
a virus. a leech.
a criminal. a piece
of human excrement.
If I want to watch him
die. what should stop me?
[metal clanging]
[screaming]
Okay. okay. okay. okay.
okay! I get it. I get it.
I broke the social contract.
so you can too now.
You’ve made your point.
Just please stop this!
[body thumps]
[blood squirting]
[William] Here’s the deal.
If he can stand up. I’ll
let you out of the car.
but he has to stand
up all the way.
That’s the deal.
Come on. get up.
Come on. Come on.
come on. get up.
[engine revving]
[Eddie screaming]
[William laughing]
You fucking motherfucker!
You fucking psycho. I’m
gonna fucking kill you!
[William] Yeah. that’s
the spirit. Eddie.
[screaming] You fucking psycho!
[William] Let’s have some anarchy!
[classical music starts]
Fuck you! Fuck you. Fuck!
[classical music plays]
Fuck you. you...
Fuck you!
[tires screeching]
Stop. slow down!
[William] What’s
your problem. Eddie?
"Street Smart Eddie." Fuck!
[William] Isn’t this
what you wanted?
Chaos. revolution. yeah!
[Eddie] Whoa!
[car honking]
[tires screeching]
[Eddie] Stop!
[William] Come on.
Eddie... Fuck! Fuck!
...you’re ruining the best
part of the song. Listen.
[shrieks]
Fucking stop!
[tires screeching]
Stop! [screams]
[William] Come on.
Eddie. have some fun.
We all get to do whatever we
want. I’m gonna be sick! Stop!
Stop the fucking car! [William]
Aren’t you happy? Come on!
I’m gonna be sick! [groans]
[William] Good. then be sick.
Stop! [William] There
are no rules here. Eddie.
Welcome to the human
jungle! Fucking stop!
[William] Yay!
Fucking stop the car!
[screaming] Help!
Stop! [William cackles]
Stop. stop. stop!
Don’t do this!
[tires screech]
[screaming]
[William] Come on.
Eddie. here we go! Yay!
No. no. no. no.
no. no! [screams]
[music dies down]
[eerie music plays]
[phone ringing]
[William] Come on.
wake up. sleepyhead.
[singsongy] Wakey-wakey!
Good morning.
[William laughing]
[groans]
What?
[William] I have news
from Amy and Sarah.
What are you talking about?
[William] I stopped
by the apartment.
No.
[William] Oh. yes.
Amy let me in and...
You went to their
apartment? No way.
[William] Yeah. yeah. 306 Myrtle
Lane. apartment number 10.
Sound familiar?
I don’t believe you.
[William] Oh. really?
Sarah was doing her homework.
She’s such a nice girl.
Why would she let a
stranger into the house?
[William] I don’t know.
but she did. You’re lying.
[William] No. I
don’t believe you.
[William] No. it
was quite easy.
I told them that I worked
for a nonprofit organization
designed to help single
mothers collect money
from deadbeat dads like you.
And I even had a
business card made up.
Very professional.
I don’t understand.
[William] Kinko’s offers a
quick turnaround. you see.
No. I mean. what the
fuck is wrong with you?
They’re not part of this. [William]
Of course they’re part of it.
You leave my family
alone. you hear me?
[William] Well. actually. we do
have a lot in common. you see.
[scoffs] You have
nothing in common.
[William] We are both
victims of your selfishness.
Victims?
I love my family. [William] No. you
only care about yourself. Eddie.
and you don’t care who you hurt.
You don’t know what
you’re talking about.
[William] You owe two years
child and spousal support.
That’s a lie. [William] No. it’s
not a lie. it’s a public record.
I ran a credit check.
You gave me your social
security number. remember?
Yeah. well I’m paying
now. every month.
[William] Two years.
I’m trying so hard...
[William] The court found
you unfit to be a daddy.
You think I don’t know?
I know Sarah loves me.
There’s nothing
you can say that...
[children chattering]
Wait...
Why are we here?
[William] Tell me. Eddie.
do you think little Sarah inherited
your street smarts? I wonder.
Just listen to me. Go. Drive.
[William] Look. there
she is. little Sarah.
waiting for you to come get her.
Oh. my God.
[William] She must know
that you’re not coming.
Oh. dear.
[engine revving]
Sarah.
Sarah!
[shouting] Sarah!
[William] It is only
a few blocks away.
but with the rising crime
rate. I wonder if she’s safe.
We shouldn’t be here.
You leave her alone.
Let’s just go. let’s
just drive away.
[engine revving]
Just stop! Stop!
Stop. stop! Fuck!
Sarah.
[intense musical buildup]
Sarah. Sarah!
You stop following my girl.
You don’t bring my
family into this.
You hear me. you fucking psycho?
Leave her alone.
Hey. hey. hey. what are
you doing? Stop. stop.
[engine starts]
What are you...
No. no. no! Stop!
Stop. stop. stop!
[tires screeching] [gasps]
Okay. okay. okay. okay.
okay. I give up. I give up.
I’m sorry I broke
into your car. okay?
I’ve never been more sorry
in my entire fucking life.
Just tell me what you
want and I’ll do it. okay?
Please. please. please
believe me. Don’t hurt her!
[car accelerating]
[William] I believe you.
But sorry is a well of pain
that goes deep. deep down.
You’re still far
from the bottom.
No. No.
She’s just a little girl! She
hasn’t done anything wrong.
I give up. I give up.
Fucking stop!
Stop!
Hey! Here! Here! Is
this what you want?
No. no. stop. Eddie. Don’t do
it. Eddie. Please. don’t do it.
No. no. no. don’t. don’t.
Well done. Eddie. I took the
bullets when I stitched you up.
Wouldn’t want to ruin
all the fun. would I?
[panting]
[William] Eddie. are you
there? It’s me. yeah.
Are you there. Eddie?
You see. the problem is
incarceration is largely...
Shoot them? Why not?
I had to do that.
That’s only my opinion. Are you
offended. Eddie? Does that offend you?
Politicians say things like.
"Let me be clear." That
would be understood.
Yeah. so we went. "It’s
okay. it’s called democracy."
Ah. a terrible word.
I’m done. [William] Say it again.
Eddie. I couldn’t hear you.
Say it again!
I said I’m done.
Let me out.
[William] What are
you doing. Eddie?
Stop it. Eddie.
Stop. Eddie. stop.
Stop it now!
Fuck this! [William] I’m
warning you. come on.
[grunts]
[William] Stop it.
Calm down! Stop it.
Eddie. I’m warning
you. Stop it.
Stop it. Stop. Stop it. Eddie!
Eddie. I’m warning you.
I said I’m fucking done!
[Eddie] Hi. lovebug.
Are you too old for that now?
No. no. you’ll
always be my lovebug.
Sorry. I really hope
that you get this
because I want you
to know that. um...
that I’m sorry.
I’m no good.
I’ve never been a
good dad to you...
and I’ve never been a
good anything to anyone.
And I. um...
I don’t know. I kind of thought
that you’d be better off
if I wasn’t around so much.
It’s all bullshit.
It’s all just excuses.
I see that now.
But being your dad was the
only thing that I’ve ever done
that meant a damn thing.
It’s the only thing
that mattered to me.
And now I’m here
at the end and...
I don’t think I’m
getting out of this one.
I can’t stop thinking about you.
I wish I spent
more time with you.
You know. I wish I
was there. I wish I...
If I could do it all
again. I’d show up. baby.
You know. I’d be there.
Whatever happens. I just. um...
I really. really.
really loved you.
I’ve just been really
bad at showing it.
Hello. Eddie.
I’m William.
You’re in my car.
You motherfucker!
[zapping] [screams]
Help!
[screams]
God. You smell
like shit. Eddie.
You’ve ruined my car.
[coughing]
[William] So you’re not a fan
of Passionate Strawberries?
Well. it happens
to be my favorite.
You gonna behave?
Zip-tie your wrists.
Pick it up.
Fuck you.
[zapping] [screaming]
Okay. okay. okay.
Now. zip-tie
yourself to the bar.
Really tight.
[zip tie tightening]
[wind howling]
Oh. whoa. It’s cold out there.
Oh. it’s raining cats and dogs.
Oh.
Oh. God. Oh. that’s good.
So. what do you think. Eddie.
of this car. this vehicle?
Huh?
Touch of genius. right?
I’m sorry. Eddie. I forgot.
You youngsters are
not too impressed
with us old dinosaurs. are you?
Now. why the hell would you be? We’re just
a bunch of old bores. right? [chuckles]
Yeah. Well. let’s see
if... What is this?
That’s a Glock. huh? Hey. you can kill
a lot of people with these things.
Let’s have a look here.
You kids like these things. huh?
Ah.
I have a surprise for you.
It’s a joint. Is that what you
guys call these things? Joints?
I’m not complaining because
it’s made legal now.
hence the great drop in our
crime rate in this country. yeah?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Okay. here we go.
[lighter clinks]
God almighty. Yuck. [chuckles]
Ugh! You smoke these things?
Holy Moses. they’re terrible.
I don’t understand
the attraction.
Holy Moses. Here.
take a hit. Eddie.
Go on. Have another!
Good. Good for you.
Anyway. I brought
something for myself.
I’ve got little snacks. These
are called gummy bears. right?
Yeah. yeah. they’re really good.
Beautiful. Yeah. it’s good.
[chuckles] Love
gummy bears. Mmm.
By the way. how is that
bullet wound of yours. Eddie?
You know. if I’d been
in your position.
being a sensible. well-adjusted.
level-headed sort of chap.
I don’t think shooting myself in the
leg would have been my first move.
but those must be your street
smarts that you’re so proud of.
So. well done. Jolly good show.
[chuckles]
Anyway.
Yeah. it’s gonna
be a long drive.
so you better eat
some. Eddie. okay?
Go on.
Have some gummy bears.
Yummy. yummy.
Enjoy them.
[classical music playing]
Okay.
Off we go.
Yes. I know. It’s...
My daughter Emma. she
loved classical music.
I think it’s terrific.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Must teach you more about
music before you die. Eddie.
[classical music continues]
When I said I was sorry.
you believed me. right?
Isn’t that what this
whole thing was about?
Mm-hmm. Hmm.
Yes. of course I
believe you. Eddie.
Everyone is sorry
once they begin to experience the
consequences of their actions. yes.
So this was your plan?
To break me. destroy
me. then just kill me?
[chuckles]
Plan? No. there’s
no plan. Eddie.
You just happened to break into
the wrong vehicle. that’s all.
You’re a petty thief
and a criminal.
and you just happened
to get away with...
Well. you got away with it
until today. so... tough titty.
So then turn me in.
[William] Turn you
in to the police? No.
I don’t care if you
go to prison. Eddie.
and I don’t care if
you don’t go to prison.
I just want to introduce you
to a little taste of hell.
And then? Well. what
does it matter. Eddie?
You were about to blow your
brains out. weren’t you?
To protect my daughter.
[William] Oh. yeah.
Tell me about it.
You know. perhaps you’ve never
experienced accountability before.
And this is what
accountability feels like
in this wonderful
human jungle of ours.
So welcome to the
gates of hell on Earth.
That’s a nice bracelet.
Did your daughter give you that?
Yeah. she gave it to me. yeah.
Got a problem with that. Eddie?
No. not a problem.
You’re playing her
favorite music.
Wearing her charm bracelet.
Sorry about that. Eddie.
[laughs softly]
What’s so funny?
What’s the joke?
What’s so funny? Yeah.
[Eddie laughs]
You got a guy chained
up in your car.
Yeah. like we’re on some kind
of fucking family road trip.
Just you and me. Daddy.
Daddy. yeah.
[both laugh] Daddy-o.
Ooh. [grunts]
Whoo! [laughing] Ooh.
The problem is. sadly. your
whole generation sucks.
Yeah. you’re scum.
You know nothing.
You’re ignorant. you
think you know everything.
and you lecture the whole world
about what you think you know.
and you know fuck all.
You gonna cancel me? Go
ahead and fucking cancel me.
Good.
Why don’t you tell me what
happened to Emma. huh?
Fuck off. [Eddie] No.
Explain it to me. I’m slow.
Slow? Okay. I’ll explain
very slowly. Eddie. okay?
You ready. Eddie? Good.
First of all. those scumbags
who robbed us at gunpoint
took everything we had. but
obviously it wasn’t enough.
Anyway. they shot her in the
neck. my little girl. Emma.
and I remember she looked at
me. and she pointed to her neck.
She said. "Daddy." and I
said. just like that...
She said. "Daddy. Daddy."
and then she died.
Yeah. I laughed because I
remember thinking how strange.
how odd it was that my little
girl was with me one moment
and suddenly bang. poof. gone.
Yeah. without warning. forever.
taken from me violently.
and for what. Eddie?
For $1500 of street smarts.
That’s why you’re
doing this. huh?
Yeah. you’re living out some kind
of Clint Eastwood Death Wishfantasy?
Yeah. go on. Make my
day. Eddie. Make my day.
We’re having fun now.
aren’t we? Yeah. [chuckles]
Yeah. [laughs]
Blow your fucking
brains over this place.
Go on. please.
Make my day.
I’m so tired of hearing
your fucking babble.
It would do me a favor.
Pull the fucking trigger.
Yeah. Scumbags like you.
off the streets. Yeah.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Yeah. I’m insane like
you. Insane like me?
Yeah. It’s people like you
drive me insane. [chuckles]
You know what you are?
You built this car...
[engine revving]
Huh? And you torture
me. That’s right.
Yeah. and you murder
people. That’s right.
Yeah. like you’re some
fucked-up wannabe Batman.
[laughs] That’s
right. You’re smart.
[chuckles] Justice.
you call it justice.
You call it justice.
[William] Yes. it’s justice.
Well. this pretend. moral
high ground. it’s bullshit.
You know what you are?
What’s that? Tell me.
You’re a sad.
lonely.
angry. old man.
Keep talking.
The world’s passing you by.
but you know what
the worst part is?
What’s that?
It’s that you’re doing all of
this in your daughter’s name.
That’s right. [groans]
Emma would be ashamed of you.
Fuck you!
Tell me to process my
grief. Go on. tell me.
And I pray to
little Jesus. yeah.
and to a little star in the sky
that her life is
better elsewhere.
[laughing]
[car accelerating]
What’s the joke? What’s funny?
Ah. Uh...
[tires screeching]
I’ve been working at this for
so long. You have no idea.
Yeah? Yeah. I think I got it.
Got what?
Street smarts. bitch.
[squelching]
[high-pitched ringing]
[crashing]
[phone chimes]
[ominous music plays]
[rattling]
[grunting]
Fuck you. Fuck you! [sobs]
[Eddie screaming]
You motherfucker!
You motherfucker.
I’ll fucking kill you!
I’ll fucking kill you.
[phone ringing]
Answer it.
Go on. Answer it.
[Sarah] Daddy?
Hey. Hey. lovebug.
It’s so good to hear
your voice. Um...
Uh. sorry. my phone’s about
to die. baby. but. um...
I got your message.
What’s going on. Daddy?
You sounded so scared.
I’m sorry. sweetie.
I didn’t mean to scare you.
What happened?
Nothing. It’s not important.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I’m okay now.
Are you sure? Because
you don’t sound okay.
I’m good. I promise.
Are you picking
me up today? 2:15.
Daddy?
Uh...
Yes.
Yes. Yes. I’ll be there.
You’re not gonna be a
fart-head again. are you?
No. Not anymore.
You’ll see. I’ll be there.
I’ll be there.
Okay. but I gotta run.
But I’ll see you at 2:15. okay?
I love you.
I love you too.
Daddy. [line beeps]
Hey. it’s over.[grunts]
Unlock the doors.
Hey.
[chuckles]
That was fun. Eddie.
A lot of fun.
[grunting]
God!
[coughs]
[Eddie grunting]
[shouts]
Come on!
[coughs. screams]
[coughing]
[panting]
[vehicle approaching]
Hey!
Hey. stop!
[driver] Geez.
buddy. you okay?
I need to pick up my daughter.
What happened here?
[tools whirring]
[bell ringing]
The fuck happened to you?
You know. I don’t wanna
know. All right. look.
Your car’s parked in pretty
deep in the other lot.
Give me. like. 40 minutes.
Gonna take too long.
My daughter needs me
to pick her up at 2:15.
2:15. You’re gonna have to
wait like everyone else.
You know what?
How much would you
give me for the van?
Hey. baby.
Dad!
I’m okay. baby.
[sniffles. cries softly]
It’s gonna be okay.
Yeah.
♪ Please ♪
♪ Let me out ♪
♪ Always ♪
♪ Is enough for you ♪
♪ Rotten years ♪
♪ Pulled you too close to me ♪
♪ Too close to breathe ♪
♪ Mystery ♪
♪ Long gone now ♪
♪ Try to live in a moment ♪
♪ Silence ♪
♪ Say you love me ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
♪ The trials ♪
♪ The crimes ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
♪ The trials ♪
♪ The crimes ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
♪ Taste ♪
♪ Let them go ♪
♪ All the way ♪
♪ Let it fall from you ♪
♪ Silence ♪
♪ Say you loved me ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
♪ The trials ♪
♪ The crimes ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
♪ The trials ♪
♪ The crimes ♪
♪ Let it be untrue ♪
[electronic music playing]
[song ends]
[dramatic music playing]
[music ends]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-